https://www.thenzteamshop.com/privacy-policy/

Place your orders before Tuesday 15th Midnight NZT to receive them on time for Christmas.
Home
PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how New Zealand Olympic Committee Incorporated (NZOC) (referred to throughout this Privacy Policy as “we”, “us” and “our”) collects, holds, uses and discloses personal information obtained through your use of our New Zealand Team website: http://thenzteamshop.com(Site).By using or accessing the Site and/or any of our services, you consent to our use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (as amended from time to time).SECTION 1 – COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe collect only the personal information that is given to us by you, or by someone we believe is authorised to provide that information to us on your behalf. When you make enquiries about our products or services through the Site or submit orders to purchase something from the Site, as part of the response or buying and selling processes, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.When you browse our Site, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.We will only use and disclose your personal information for the purposes for which it was collected (or otherwise as required or authorised by law). This may include using your personal information for the following purposes:to assist in completing a transaction or an order for products or services through the Site; to provide customer service and support in respect of our products or services, or the Site and the functionality and services offered through it; for email marketing (with your consent, we may send you emails about our Site, new products and other updates); to comply with relevant laws and regulations; for administrative purposes; and for any other specific purpose which we notify you of at the time your personal information is collected.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary purpose, like marketing, we will ask you directly for your express consent and provide you with an opportunity to say no. If after you consent to us using your personal information for marketing purposes you change your mind and no longer wish to receive direct marketing from NZOC, you may withdraw your consent at any time, by:emailing us at accounts@olympic.org.nz; or mailing us at:New Zealand Olympic Committee
PO Box 37-774, Parnell, Auckland 1151, New Zealand.SECTION 2 - DISCLOSUREFor the purposes described in section 1 above, we may disclose your personal information:to our service providers and suppliers (including our on-line retail / e-commerce partner Red Box Digital) as well as other third party service providers who help us with content and administration of the Site and/or deliver products and services to you for the purposes of the services that they provide to us; to anyone who hosts or maintains data centres, service platforms and other infrastructure and systems on behalf of us, where your personal information is processed and/or stored for the purposes of the services that they provide to us; anyone to whom our assets or business (or any part of it) is transferred; where you have otherwise consented; or as otherwise required or authorised by law.SECTION 3 - MAGENTO (our online e-commerce platform)Our store is hosted on Magento. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
Your data is stored through Magento’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.PaymentIf you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Magento stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.For more insight, please visit Magento’s website https://magento.comSECTION 4 - THIRD-PARTY PAYMENT GATEWAYS AND PAYMENT PROCESSORSCertain third-party payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. If you choose to use any such providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. Therefore, if you elect to proceed with a transaction utilising the services of a third-party to process your payment, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that third party or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our Site or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our Site’s terms of service.LinksWhen you click on links on our Site, they may direct you away from our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.SECTION 5 - SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.SECTION 6 – YOUR RIGHTS TO ACCESS AND CORRECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONIf you wish to obtain confirmation that we hold personal information about you and to access that information, or you wish to request a correction to your personal information that we hold, please contact us at the contact details set out in section 10 of this Privacy Policy.You may also amend your personal information associated with your account by updating your account details.If you request access to, or a copy of, your personal information, we will provide you with a copy of the personal information we keep about you. However, we reserve the right to charge you a reasonable amount for providing copies of any personal information you request, to take into account the time, cost and effort involved.If you request a correction to your personal information and we agree that your personal information needs correcting, an amended record of your personal information will be provided back to you. If we do not agree to your request for a correction, you may request that we take reasonable steps to attach to the information a statement of correction sought but not made.SECTION 7 - COOKIESCookies are small information files that are sent to your browser and may be stored on your computer. We may use cookies to provide you with information in relation to the Site, to improve the Site, and to personalise your use of the Site. We have listed below the cookies that we use so that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not. If you wish to opt-out of the use of cookies on the Site, you can do so by opening a private browsing window on your browser.List of cookies we collectThe table below lists the cookies that NZOC or Magento collect and what information they store.Cookie NameCookie DescriptionFORM_KEYStores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.PHPSESSIDYour session ID on the server.GUEST-VIEWAllows guests to view and edit their orders.PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CARTA link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.STFInformation on products you have emailed to friends.STOREThe store view or language you have selected.USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIEIndicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.MAGE-CACHE-SESSIDFacilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.MAGE-CACHE-STORAGEFacilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATIONFacilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUTFacilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.SECTION-DATA-IDSFacilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSIONFacilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.X-MAGENTO-VARYFacilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSIONFacilitates translation of content to other languages.MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGEFacilitates translation of content to other languages.SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENTBy using this Site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your country, state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your country, state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this Site.SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here of the key changes that have been made.
If our Store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.SECTION 10 - QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact our Chief Financial Officer at accounts@olympic.org.nz or by mail at:New Zealand Olympic CommitteeAttn: Chief Financial OfficerPO Box 37-774, Parnell, Auckland 1151
‹
›
×
×
Previous
Next
